promolotto.com 2013-07-22

# Promo Lotto - Manual Traffic Exchange - Free Website Traffic - Increase Web Traffic

###  **Privacy Policy**

###  **When you provide us with personal information, it is handled according  to the following policy:  
 **

  * **Customer Feedback and Support.**    
Provides a method for requesting product information and support services from   
PromoLotto. It is also used to tell us how we can improve our products/services to better meet your needs.  
 
  * **Correspondence:  **  
Correspondence received by PromoLotto is kept strictly confidential and is not given or sold to third parties.  
PromoLotto does not send unsolicited email advertisements under any circumstance and is not responsible for the actions of its affiliates.  
If you feel an affiliate has abused our Zero-Tolerance spam policy, please contact us by forwarding the offending email.We will contact you with updates, offers and relevant information as well as a newsletter as part of our service. If you do not wish to receive these, then you can delete your account in the main member's area at anytime.  
 
  * **Double Opt-In:  
**After joining PromoLotto, you will receive a confirmation email containing your login information. To activate your membership, you must verify and acknowledge that you joined.  
    
  * **Personal Information:  
**Sensitive information is not gathered or stored at PromoLotto.com.   
Authorized third parties  such as payment processors, may need access to some of your personal information.  
If we need to ship a product to you, we must share your name and address with shipping companies, etc.  
  
  * **Linked web sites:**  
PromoLotto facilitates links and advertisements for its members.   
Since we do not control the content of these web sites, we encourage you to review the privacy policies posted on these (and all) third party sites.  
These third party websites may or may not contain cookies for end-user data retrieval purposes.  
 
  * **Cookies:  
**PromoLotto does use cookie data so that the site can function properly by confirming when you are logged into or out of this website. 

  * **DoubleClick DART Cookie**

.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.promolotto.com.  
.:: Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to www.promolotto.com and other sites on the Internet.   
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html 

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include .......   
Google Adsense   
Clickbank 

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.promolotto.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. 

www.promolotto.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. 

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.promolotto.com's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. 

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites. 

**This policy was last updated September, 2011.**
